<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Woojae</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Woojae</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 09:24:11 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Fix Posture</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/fix-posture/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Aug 2024 09:24:11 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/fix-posture/</guid>
      <description>During my time in Korea, one of my main goals is to work on improving my posture. I&amp;rsquo;ve struggled with poor posture for most of my life, which has led to an unattractive hunchback and constant back pain. Now that I have some time off, I&amp;rsquo;m determined to correct it.&#xA;I&amp;rsquo;ve done some research using ChatGPT and YouTube, and this is what I came up with. Let&amp;rsquo;s see if works.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hugo Installation</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/hugo-installation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Aug 2024 11:00:33 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/hugo-installation/</guid>
      <description>I’ve successfully migrated my website to Hugo. The whole point of this move was to build a simple, no-nonsense webpage that’s free to host, scales infinitely, and will stand the test of time. With Hugo, the site is statically rendered, so all I have to do is compress my files and upload them to any web server. The content is written in Markdown, I’m confident will stick around for the long haul.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Use Terraform Dynamics</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/terraform-dynamic/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2024 09:40:33 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/terraform-dynamic/</guid>
      <description>How to Use Terraform Dynamics Today, we&amp;rsquo;re focusing on a particularly powerful feature: Terraform Dynamics. This tool is essential for writing more efficient and maintainable code by helping you adhere to the DRY (Don&amp;rsquo;t Repeat Yourself) principle.&#xA;Why You Should Care About Terraform Dynamics Let’s get one thing straight: if you enjoy writing the same block of code over and over again, this post isn’t for you. Terraform dynamics is for the lazy (read: efficient) engineers who believe that copy-pasting is a crime punishable by endless debugging sessions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My First Post</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2024 20:10:06 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>Introduction I&amp;rsquo;ve finally decided to retire my old Tumblr page. It&amp;rsquo;s honestly surprising that it’s still functioning after a decade of neglect, but the time has come to move on. I&amp;rsquo;m transitioning to Hugo, a static site generator. I chose Hugo for my new website because it allows me to host it for free, and a static site offers the scalability and longevity I’m looking for. More complex setups eventually break down as frameworks become obsolete.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
